vfc.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy :: VF Corporation (VFC)

VF Corporation ("VF") recognizes that you care how information about you is used and shared and respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes what information we may collect from you, how we collect that information, how we use that information, and the choices you have regarding your information. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this website. This Privacy Policy does not reflect practices with respect to information gathered by the VF Corporation family of brands, through other websites or through off-line means. The term "we" as used in this Privacy Policy may include our third-party service providers, particularly with respect to the collection, use and storage of information. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please e-mail [ **corporate_communications@vfc.com**](mailto:corporate_communications@vfc.com).

This Privacy Policy was last updated October 27, 2016. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. Please check back periodically for further updates and changes.

**Collection and Use of Information.**

VF, itself or through its third party providers, collects on this website information that you voluntarily provide along with certain automatically collected information such as your IP address and cookies.

"Personal Information" means any information relating to your use of this website and that specifically identifies you. We may collect, generate, retain and use your Personal Information for our own internal purposes in connection with the facilitation, recording and processing of any requests, communications, or interactions you may have via our website.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic and geographic information, which may assist in the delivery of content, identifying preferences and site usage statistics.

We use cookies, when needed, to deliver content specific to your interests and when applicable to save your password or sign up information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. You may set your browser to refuse cookies. If you make that choice, please understand that you may experience diminished functionality and content delivery. Additionally you may not be eligible for any specials and / or promotions we may offer our websites users.

Your Personal Information will not be sold, rented, shared, disseminated or otherwise disclosed except as described in this Privacy Policy or if disclosure is required by law.

We may share your information with the VF Corporation family of brands  (including, for example, The North Face®, Vans®, Timberland®, Nautica®, Kipling®, Wrangler®, Lee®, Jansport® and Reef®) and may also receive information about you from other brands held by VF Corporation.

We may share information with certain third parties that perform services on our behalf. We use third-party companies to provide Internet data hosting and to help us measure and determine how visitors use our website and the effectiveness of our website and promotions in order to help us improve and optimize our website and the products and services we offer.

Data security is important to VF and we have instituted security procedures and measures to protect our servers and networks that store personal information. Unfortunately, no transmission of information over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and, therefore, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information.

This website may contain links to or from websites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply ("Linked Websites"). Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not reflect the practices regarding information collection, use and disclosure of Linked Websites or the owners or operators of those Linked Websites. Your use of Linked Websites will be governed by the terms of use, privacy policies and other terms, notices and policies set forth on or referenced in those Linked Websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave this website and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit.

**Automated E-Mail.**  

Keeping our customers and shareholders informed is a priority at VF. You may request to join our mailing list using this link [ir.vfc.com/email-alerts](http://ir.vfc.com/email-alerts) and receive occasional e-mails regarding new site content, events and investor information. To unsubscribe use the following link [ir.vfc.com/unsubscribe](http://ir.vfc.com/unsubscribe).  Please note that unsubscribing will not stop content that is generated for distribution or is otherwise queued for transmission to you prior to the time when we can implement your request. After you have unsubscribed your information will be retained as a record of opt-in/opt-out request.

VF Corporation  
105 Corporate Center Blvd.  
Greensboro, NC 2740
